// Storing all questions and answers //

export const questions = [
  {
    number: 1,
    question: "Which is a form of a Cyber Attack?",
    answer: "Phishing",
    options: ["Spear Fishing", "Fishing", "Email phishing", "Phishing"],
  },

  {
    number: 2,
    question: "What does the term “Black Hat” Hacker mean?",
    answer: "Individuals who use their skills for malicious activities",
    options: [
      "Individuals who use their skills to help fight against cyber criminals",
      "Individuals who use their skills for malicious activities",
      "Network Analyst",
      "Penetration Testers",
    ],
  },

  {
    number: 3,
    question:
      "What percentage of UK companies have reported a data breach incident to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) in the past 12 months?",
    answer: "37%",
    options: ["37%", "10%", "12%", "95%"],
  },

  {
    number: 4,
    question: "What type of Malware uses Denial of Service attacks (DoS)?",
    answer: "Botnet",
    options: ["Virus", "Worm", "Botnet", "Trojan"],
  },

  {
    number: 5,
    question: "What type of Malware aims to extort money from the victim?",
    answer: "Ransomware",
    options: ["Trojan", "Spyware", "Worm", "Ransomware"],
  },

  {
    number: 6,
    question:
      "What type of Firewall covers the entire network, filters traffic coming into the network from the internet and traffic going back out?",
    answer: "Boundary Firewall",
    options: [
      "Host-based Firewall",
      "Home-based Firewall",
      "Boundary Firewall",
      "Software Based Firewall",
    ],
  },

  {
    number: 7,
    question:
      "It is recommended updates are done within how long of their release.",
    answer: "Within 14 days",
    options: [
      "Within 30 days",
      "Within 14 days",
      "Yearly",
      "It is not important",
    ],
  },

  {
    number: 8,
    question: "Which of the following is Firewall Best Practice?",
    answer: "All The Above",
    options: [
      "Change the admin password of the router",
      "Block all ports that are not used",
      "Turn off Universal Plug and Play devices (uPnP)",
      "All The Above",
    ],
  },

  {
    number: 9,
    question:
      "What percentage can Cyber Essentials protect your company from the most common Cyber Security Threats?",
    answer: "80%",
    options: ["5%", "10%", "100%", "80%"],
  },

  {
    number: 10,
    question:
      "All applications or code that is of unknown source should be run in what mode?",
    answer: "Application Sandboxing",
    options: [
      "Application Whitelisting",
      "Anti-Virus",
      "Application Whistleblowing",
      "Application Sandboxing",
    ],
  },
];
